College of Arts and Sciences Collection, 1937-1973
University of Houston Libraries
- Subject Files (Box 1-29)
  - Science and Research Bldg. - Equipment, 1966-1972 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Science and Research Building Floor Plans, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Science and Research Building - Keying, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Science and Research Building Moving, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Science and Research Building Parking, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Science and Research Building Space, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Science Building, 1960-1971 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Science Building Alterations, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Science Building Remodeling, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Scientific Writing, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - SCMLA - Houston Meeting, November 1969 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Sea Grant Program, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Second Bachelor's Degree, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Segelcke, Miss Tore, 1956-1958 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Self-Study, U of H, 1964-1968 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Senate Bill 2710, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Senate - Minutes of Meetings, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Shartle, Gretchen, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Shrine Chanters, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Sick Leave Regulations, 1952-1958 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Sigma Xi, 1959-1966 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Silber, John, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Silver Anniversary, 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Singer, Walter E., 1960-1968 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Singletary, Otis A., 1960 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Skinner Teaching Machine, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Small Class Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Small Class Reports, 1967-1972 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Social Science, 1952-1955 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Social Security, 1955-1965 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Sociology - Advanced Degrees Completed, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Sociology Department, 1955-1972 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - South Central Modern Language Association, 1955-1959 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - South Central Modern Language Association, 1958-1962 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - South Central Modern Language Association, 1963-1965 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - South Central Modern Language Association, 1966-1971 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - South Central Modern Language Association Bulletin, 1968-1972 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - South Central Modern Language Association Bulletin, 1961-1970 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1965-1971 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools Commission on Colleges, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools Dallas, Texas Meeting, 1965-1968 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools Standards folder, 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1952-1960 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Southern Association Visitation Committee University of Tampa, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Southern Association Visitation Committee University of the South, 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Southern Conference on Language Teaching, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Southern Historical Association, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Southern Humanities Conference, 1965-1971 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Southern Humanities Review, 1966-1971 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Southern Methodist University, 1955-1966 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Southern Political Science Association, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Space, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Space Allocation Committee, 1969/70 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Space Allocation Committee, 1969/70 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Space Allocation Committee, 1970/71 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Space Allocation Committee, 1971/72 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Space Allocation Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Space - Buildings, etc., September 1961-August 1966 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Space - Building, etc., 1966-1969 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Space Survey, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Spanish - Advanced Degrees Completed, 1964-1966 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Spanish Department, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Special Services for Disadvantaged Students, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Speech - Advanced Degrees Completed, 1962-1967 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Speech and Hearing Therapy, Advanced Degrees Completed, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Speech and Hearing Therapy, Advance Degrees Pending, 1954-1967 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Speech and Hearing Therapy - Major in, 1963-1966 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Speech Clinic, 1959-1971 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Speech Department, 1952-1966 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Speech Department, 1967-1972 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Speech - New Instructional Degree Granting Program, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Speech - New Instructional Degree Granting Program, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Speech Pathology and Audiology, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Speech Pathology and Audiology, 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Speech Pathology and Audiology at Memorial Hospital, 1964-1970 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Speech - Proposed Doctor of Philosophy Degree, 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Spelling Bee, 1955-1958 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Spencer, Betty Jo, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Staff Conference, 1961-1968 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Staff Study of European Extension Courses, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Stanford Conference on Latin America, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Starck, Professor Taylor, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - State Audit Class Rolls, 1967-1971 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - State Fair Project, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - State Regulations, 1963-1969 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - State Support - University of Houston, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Statistical Information Re Arts and Sciences, 1955-1958 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Statistics, Comparative, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Stokes-Pantillion, June, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Stone, Sada Lou, 1959-1962 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Storage and Supply Inventory, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Store List, 1967-1971 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Street, Julian, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - St. Thomas - University of Houston Title III - Grant Proposal, 1966-1968 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Student Activities, 1961-1967 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Student Activity Hour, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Student Advisory Council, 1968-1972 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Student Advocate, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Student Association, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Student Correspondence A-D, 1966-1972 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Student Correspondence E-H, 1966-1972 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Student Correspondence I-L, 1966-1971 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Student Correspondence M-P, 1966-1972 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Student Correspondence Q-Z, 1977-1972 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Student Counseling, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Student Course and Teacher Evaluation Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Student Excuses, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Student-Faculty Committee on Academic Affairs, 1967-1971 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Student Involvement (Committee on), 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Student Life Policies, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Student Load Statistics, 1960-1967 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Student Opportunity Service, 1968-1972 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Student Organizations, 1957-1972 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Student Publications, 1961-1972 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Student Roster, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Students Withdrawals Committee, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Study Abroad Programs, Others, 1968-1972 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Study Abroad Programs, University of Houston, 1966-1972 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Summer Institutes, 1967-1972 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Summer Session Length, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Summer Study Abroad for American Students, 1961-1970 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Sunday Evening Club, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Suniland Furniture Company, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Superior Students, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Suspension Report, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Swedish Consulate, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Tax-sheltered Annuity, 1963-1971 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - TBA Classes, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Teacher Certification, 1959-1966 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Teacher - Directed Brochure, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Teacher Education, Committee on, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Teacher Load Reports, 1958-1970 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Teacher Retirement, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Teacher Training, Committee on, 1955-1968 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Teacher Training Programs, 1958-1967 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Teachers' Insurance and Annuity Association, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Teaching Excellence Award, 1968-1972 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Teaching Fellows, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Teaching Load (University of Houston), 1960-1968 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Teaching Load (University of Houston), 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Teaching Load Analysis, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Teaching Loads Accountability, 1968-1972 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Techniques of Teaching Foreign Languages, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Technology Committee, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Technology Four Year Degree, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Technology Four Year Degree, 1964-1966 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Telefunken Information, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Telephones, 1959-1965 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Telephones, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Telephones, 1968-1973 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Telephones Science and Research Building, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Television, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Television Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Television - Educational, 1956-1965 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Television - Teaching by, 1955-1965 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Tenure, 1954-1965 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Tenure, 1966-1972 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Terminal Degrees, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Texas A & M College, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Texas Academy of Science, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Texas Assembly, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Texas Association of College Teachers, 1967-1971 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Texas Association of Music Schools, 1960-1968 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Texas Association Standards, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Texas Commission on Higher Education, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Texas Education Agency, 1956-1963 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Texas Education Agency, 1964-1971 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Texas Fine Arts Commission, 1967-1970 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Texas Libraries, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Texas Medical Association, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Texas Observer, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Texas Public Interest Research Group (TexPIRG), 1972 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Texas Southern University, 1957-1966 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Texas Speech Association, 1960-1966 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc., 1970 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Theatre Guild, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Themis (Project), 1968-1970 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Thesis Writing at the University of Houston, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Thomas Case (Joe York Thomas), 1961 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Tinsley, Mr. Royal, 1960-1963 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Title IV and Title V, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Title VI - Matching Grants for Under Graduate Teaching Equipment, 1968-1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Toth, Andor, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Traffic and Security - Office of, 1962-1972 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Transfer Core Curriculum, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Transportation Tax, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Travel, 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Trees, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Trimester Plan, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Tuition, 1955-1971 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Tuition Benefit - Faculty and Their Families, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Tulane Self-Study, 1956-1968 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Tutorial Program, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Typewriter Repair, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Unemployment Compensation, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - UNESCO (UN Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization), 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - United Fund, 1954-1965 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - United Fund, 1966-1972 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - United States Steel Teaching Awards, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Universidad Autonoma de Guadalajara, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Universidad de Monterrey, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Universities - Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - University Admissions Committee, 1956-1972 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - University Athletics Committee, undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - University Auditoria - Cullen, Liberal Arts, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - University Bands Departmental Five Year Plan, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - University Center, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - University Council, 1965/66 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - University Council, 1966/67 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - University Council (1 of 2), 1967/68 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - University Council (2 of 2), 1967/68 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - University Council, 1968/69 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - University Council, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - University Council, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - University Council (1 of 2), 1970/71 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - University Council (2 of 2), 1970/71 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - University Council, 1971/72 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - University Council, 1972/73 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - University Development Council, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - University Festival, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - University Governance, 1970-1972 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - University Issues Conference, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - University Library Committee, 1966-1972 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - University Miscellaneous, 1966-1972 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - University Planning, 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - University Press, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - University Press Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - University Research Committee, 1966-1972 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - University Research Grant Program I, Humanities, 1966-1971 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - University Research Interdisciplinary Programs, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - University Television Laboratory, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - University of Florida Materials and Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - University of Florida Materials and Correspondence, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - University of Houston Foundation, 1959-1969 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - University of Houston Scholars, undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - University of Kentucky, 1960-1966 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - University of Louisville, 1963-1968 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - University of Michigan, 1960-1968 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - University of South Carolina, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - University of St. Thomas, 1960-1968 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - University of Texas, 1956-1972 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - University of Texas Dental School, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - University of Texas - Division of Extension, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - University of Texas - Medical Branch, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - University of West Florida, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - University of West Florida, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - University of West Florida, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - University of West Florida, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - University of West Florida - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Unspecified Major in Arts and Sciences, 1960-1962 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Upward Bound Program, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Urban Studies Joint Committee on Joint Center, 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare - General, 1964-1966 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Utility Failure, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Vacation, 1955-1967 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Van Evera, Dr. B. D., 1959 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Vehicles - Motor, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Warren, Reverend Thomas B., 1953-1959 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Water Resources, 1966-1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Wauchope, Professor Robert, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Wayne State University, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Weingarten, Joe, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Welch Chair, 1965-1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Welch Foundation, 1954-1966 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Welch Foundation, 1967-1973 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Welch, Louie, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Werlin Go Round, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - White House Fellows, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Whitney Foundation, 1956-1961 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Williams, Bobby Gail, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Williams, Clayton W., 1954-1957 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Williams, Clayton W., 1958-1964 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Williams, Pamela, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Williamson, J. E., 1953-1960 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Women's Club, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Wood, Dr. Ernest, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Woodrow Wilson Centennial, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 1959-1970 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Work-Study Program, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - World Affairs Bulletin, 1967-1973 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - World Institute for World Peace, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Xerox Model 813, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Yale University, 1957-1960 (Box 29, Folder 31)